Risk everything. Regret nothing.
Regretting You is a romance, drama film directed by Josh Boone.
Morgan Grant and her daughter Clara explore what's left behind after a devastating accident reveals a shocking
betrayal and forces them to confront family secrets, redefine love, and rediscover each other.
Morgan Grant, played by Allison Williams.
Clara Grant, played by Mckenna Grace.
Jonah Sullivan, played by Dave Franco.
Miller Adams, played by Mason Thames.
Lexie, played by Sam Morelos.
Chris Grant, played by Scott Eastwood.
Regretting You (marketed as Colleen Hoover's Regretting You) is a 2025 romantic
drama film based on the 2019 novel of the same name by Colleen Hoover.
It is directed by Josh Boone from a screenplay by Susan McMartin.
It stars Allison Williams, Mckenna Grace, Dave Franco, and Mason Thames.
The film premiered at the Zoo Palast in Berlin on October 12, 2025, and was released by Constantin Film in
Germany on October 23, 2025 and by Paramount Pictures in the United States on October 24.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics, but was a modest box-office
success, grossing $90.5 million worldwide on a budget of $30 million.
The film explores themes of high school, based on novel or book, aunt
niece relationship, north carolina, death of father.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.